Let's get into a mostly upright position, take your thumbs here, and place them under this
frequency,
and put it under your armpits like this.
You're going to take a deep breath in through your nose,
adopt a slightly straighter posture for the body because we are going to work with the central channel.
Inhale through the nose,
and exhale through the mouth the notion of self, your mental toxins, selfishness.
You're releasing them from within, so inhale.
Exhale out the unnecessary.
Inhale.
One last time, inhale.
To have clear awareness, now place your longest finger at the level of the nasion.
Plug the right nostril.
You will
inhale through the left nostril.
And think of inhaling prana.
So focus on this level of prana.
Inhale through the left nostril.
Plug the other side and exhale through the right nostril.
You re-inhale through the right nostril.
You shift and exhale through the left nostril.
You repeat the cycle.
Inhale prana.
The air, the light, the vibration, through the left nostril, all
gently.
Exhale through the right nostril.
Re-inhale one more time through the right nostril.
Exhale through the left nostril.
Do it one last time.
Gently inhale through the left nostril.
Exhale through the right nostril.
Little by little if you do this
from time to time,
you will open two small channels here
which will open the sinus space
and will enhance clarity of thought.
We must open the central channel.
To do this, we will use
the pressure of prana.
We will do a mula bandha.
This means we will contract the perineum.
First, we will inhale.
We will do a mula bandha.
We inflate here, then I contract the perineum,
pull in the belly and lift the diaphragm to elevate the air bowl upward,
I tuck in my chin, close the glottis,
and gradually bring a sensation as if I am applying this pressure to open here.
We inhale, bringing the pranic air bowl into the belly,
you pull in, do a slight pelvic tilt, close the glottis,
You tilt and lift the diaphragm to the top.
And you release.
There, you open your central channel in the form of a symbol.
Inhale once more.
The last time, I inhale.
Now, you empty the air completely, as much as you can, and
in the end, through the emptiness, you lift your diaphragm, like
this, and then you lower it, let me show you.
This will warm up the body a bit
and at the same time, you will open things up a bit.
You will just take your hands
and you will open and stretch a bit
all the meridians
to have your hands well open
and your body ready to work.
Like this.
We bring chi into the hands.
There you go, place yourself in a meditative state you can.
And close your eyes.
And become aware of prana.
Prana like a means, like a vehicle.
Remember that prana is air.
It is this light and this energy in
the form of vibration.
Somewhere, you are nourished by prana.
If you become aware of this quality, you
will become aware of what we call the whole.
If you are aware of your breathing in this three-dimensionality,
you become...
the whole. It’s so simple that we often don't do it. In a way,
we can say
that healing is the healing of disease, it’s an awareness. At some point, you won’t
talk about disease anymore, but about a low vibration. So if you know how to
raise your vibration, if you know how to raise this frequency, you
will achieve healing. This is for
as a therapist, you always have to raise your vibration or neutralize it.
You must rise to become untouchable.
One should not particularly perceive this detail, otherwise, one falls into pride.
In the end, you must also give everything back, all of it.
This is where we must be in a state of non-wanting.
In a way,
Whether we are aware or not, we pass through prana.
Be in the time of non-judgment.
And now the patient will ask you to place them at the level that suits them best.
This can be visceral, cranial, spinal, anything.
You just need to be attentive and follow the present movement.
In a way, the only thing that exists is harmony.
And harmony is achieved through the complementarity of duality in the continuation
of the equality of the other.
Often, it is pride to give an answer before the question.
Often, without realizing it, we create reference points, we create questions for the patient.
Free yourself from this.
A person does not create their disease, they endure it.
It is a response to the question they have asked, more or less consciously.
Breathe not by your will, the will to help the other which
can ultimately cause more harm than good.
Breathe in prana, raise your vibration.
One way to raise your vibration is to become aware that
each word is a vibration.
Eliminate from your vocabulary as much as possible the words that have a low frequency.
You will cleanse your inner diamond. This is where you need to become conscious. Each
word,
each gesture, each glance is a vibration. Raise your vibration. It’s as if the
earth needs it. Be like weavers of light. Each
time you have a thought,
it goes into the akasha and it is woven into the great web. We
have the right to this consciousness.
There, you can feel a vibration in your heart, like little
sparkles.